Why do black people, in your opinion, think that Trump was better for us than Biden?
I ain't faded out. I don't know.
I hear black folks say like, oh, you know, because Trump gave us money. Trump gave us checks.
Oh, I know. Now, let me say now he was good. Now, listen, I'm gonna give Trump some props
right here. The only time you'll ever hear from me. He is a master at propaganda.
So people don't know that he was fighting. So when the stimulus checks came out,
he was fighting to make sure that his actual signature was on the checks.
People probably, they could have had their money earlier, but Trump was fighting to make sure
that his name was on that check. So people would be perceiving that the money came from him when it
didn't. That was the act of Congress. Number one, same thing with the food boxes in the midst of
COVID. He had to make sure it was a letter and all the food boxes from him. Like he didn't went into
his own garden and pick this stuff for them. And he takes advantage of what people don't know,
which is they don't understand how government functions.
We do.
Now.
Now I am ready to go to keep PowerPoint as a person.
Und